Guide to the Confederate Imprint collection, 1855-1879 MS 071
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Crandall Numbers; 1855-1867, 227678
  - C.S.A. an act to allow commissioned officers of the army rations and the privilege of purchasing clothing from the quartermaster's department, 1863; 228441 (Box 3, Folder C354)
  - C.S.A. An act to grant a special copyright to W.J. Hardee and S.H. Gretzel for Hardee's Rifle and Infantry Tactics, 1863; 228440 (Box 3, Folder C355)
  - C.S.A. An act to establish a Bureau of Foreign Supplies, 1863; 228439 (Box 3, Folder C356)
  - C.S.A. Joint resolution for the relief of Major W.F.Haines, 1863; 228438 (Box 3, Folder C358)
  - C.S.A. An act to provide for wounded and disabled officers and soldiers an asylum to be called "The Veteran Soldiers Home", 1863; 228437 (Box 3, Folder C360)
  - C.S.A. A bill to provide for the reduction of the currency, 1863; 228436 (Box 3, Folder C362)
  - [House of Representatives-Secret Session] An act to levy additional taxes.. 6p. (photocopy), 1863; 228435 (Box 3, Folder C363)
  - C.S.A. [House of Representatives-Secret Session] An act to tax, fund, and limit the currency, 1863; 228434 (Box 3, Folder C366)
  - C.S.A. An act repealing existing, and regulating future, exemptions from military service, 1864; 228433 (Box 3, Folder C368)
  - C.S.A. [secret] Amendment by Mr. Swan, Jan. 5, 1864; 228432 (Box 3, Folder C370)
  - C.S.A. An act to increase the efficiency of the Army... Negroes, 1864; 228431 (Box 3, Folder C371)
  - C.S.A. [Secret Session] A bill to amend an act entitled "An act to lay taxes for the common defence and carry on the government of the C.S." approved April 24, 1863, 1864; 228430 (Box 3, Folder C374)
  - C.S.A. An act to increase the effective force of the "Provisionl Army of the Confederate States", 1864; 228429 (Box 3, Folder C375)
  - C.S.A. An act to provide additional compensation for the soldiers of the army of the C.S. and the families of those who die in service, 1864; 228428 (Box 3, Folder C376)
  - C.S.A. An act to make additional appropriations for the support of the government of the Confederate States of America, for the fiscal year ending June 30, 1864, 228427 (Box 3, Folder C378)
  - C.S.A. [secret session] Finance proposition in lieu of first six sections of committee bill insert, 1864; 228426 (Box 3, Folder C379)
  - C.S.A. House of Representatives [Secret] Resolutions of Instructions, Jan. 9, 1864; 228425 (Box 3, Folder C380)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions expressive of the determination of Georgia to prosecute the present war with the utmost vigor and energy, 1864; 228424 (Box 3, Folder C382)
  - C.S.A. House of Representatives Mr. Chilton's Amendments, Jan. 12, 1864; 228423 (Box 3, Folder C384)
  - C.S.A. Proposition of finance, 1864; 228422 (Box 3, Folder C385)
  - C.S.A. Substitute of Mr. Boteler for Mr. Wolcox's bill. An act to provide for the payment of horses killed, captured, lost or permanently disabled in the C.S. service, 1864; 228421 (Box 3, Folder C386)
  - C.S.A. [Secret session] A bill to regulate the currency, 1864; 228420 (Box 3, Folder C388)
  - C.S.A. Congress. House of Representatives. Committee on Deceased Soldiers' Claims. Gen. Tochman's Case, 1864; 228419 (Box 4, Folder C389)
  - C.S.A. An act to provide payment for slaves impressed under state laws, and lost in the public service, 1864; 228418 (Box 4, Folder C390)
  - C.S.A. House An act to suppress abuses in the Quartermaster and Commissary Departments, 1864; 228417 (Box 4, Folder C391)
  - C.S.A. House an act extending the privilege of purchasing clothing at government cost, to all persons in its employment, who have been discharged for [sic] the army on account of wounds received or disease contracted whilst in the service, 1864; 228416 (Box 4, Folder C393)
  - C.S.A. An act to authorize the impressment of meat for the use of the army, under certain circumstances, 1864; 228415 (Box 4, Folder C398)
  - C.S.A. An act amendatory of an act entitled "An act to put an end to the exemption from military service of those who have heretofore furnished substitutes" approved Jan 5 1864, 228414 (Box 4, Folder C400)
  - C.S.A. An act supplemental to the several acts relating to military courts, 1864; 228413 (Box 4, Folder C401)
  - C.S.A. [Resolutions transmitted] to the Hon. Speaker of the House, Decatur, Georgia, Jan. 27, 1864, 228412 (Box 4, Folder C406)
  - C.S.A. A bill supplemental to the several acts in relation to public printing, 1864; 228411 (Box 4, Folder C412)
  - C.S.A. Joint resolutions in reference to the treatment of colored troops 4p., Feb. 15, 1864; 228410 (Box 4, Folder C413)
  - C.S.A. Congress. House of Representative. A bill to amend "An act to lay additional taxes", 1864; 228409 (Box 4, Folder C414)
  - House bill no.9 A bill to organize a corps of scouts and signal guards, 1864; 228408 (Box 4, Folder C415)
  - C.S.A. A bill to amend an act to allow commissioned officers of the army rations, 1864; 228407 (Box 4, Folder C416)
  - C.S.A. Joint resolutions of the legislature of Louisiana, 1864; 228406 (Box 4, Folder C417)
  - [House bill no.25] An act to establish a bureau of foreign supplies, 1864; 228405 (Box 4, Folder C418)
  - C.S.A. An act to provide a fund... for the relief of disabled soldiers and seamen, 1864; 228404 (Box 4, Folder C419)
  - C.S.A. Joint resolutions of the State of Texas, 1864; 228403 (Box 4, Folder C421)
  - C.S.A. An act to establish the court for the investigation of claims, 1864; 228402 (Box 4, Folder C422)
  - C.S.A. An act to amend an act to regulate impeachments, 1864; 228401 (Box 4, Folder C423)
  - C.S.A. An act to amend an act to increase the efficiency of the army, 1864; 228400 (Box 4, Folder C424)
  - [House bill no.11] A bill to provide for the settlement of claims for the property, 1864; 228399 (Box 4, Folder C426)
  - [House bill no.28] An act to establish a Bureau of Foreign Supplies... 6p., 1864; 228398 (Box 4, Folder C427)
  - C.S.A. An act to provide for the appointment of commissioned, 1864; 228397 (Box 4, Folder C428)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions of the Legislature of the State of Mississippi... [on suspension of] the writ of habeas corpus, 1864; 228396 (Box 4, Folder C429)
  - C.S.A. [House no.102] An act to provide for the sage custody, printing, publication, and distribution of the laws, and to provide for the appointment of an additional clerk in the Department of Justice., 1864; 228395 (Box 4, Folder C430)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.93] An act for organization of the Bureau of Conscription and the appointment of officers in said Bureau, 1864; 228394 (Box 4, Folder C435)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.121] An act to provide for the settlement of certain matters of account growing out of purchases of property, 1864; 228393 (Box 4, Folder C437)
  - C.S.A. [House Bill no.123] An act making appropriations for the support of the government of the C.S.A. from July 1 to December 31, 1864 and to supply a deficiency, 228392 (Box 4, Folder C439)
  - C.S.A. [House Bill no.124] An act making appropriations for the postal service of the C.S.A. for the year 1862 and 1863, 1864; 228391 (Box 4, Folder C440)
  - Joint Resolution requiring the Settlement of the Accounts of the Post-Office Dept. prior to the first day of July 1863, 228390 (Box 4, Folder C441)
  - Preamble and resolution [suggesting the removal of the present Secretary of the Treasury, 1864; 228389 (Box 4, Folder C442)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions declaring the supremacy of the civil over the military law, 1864; 228388 (Box 4, Folder C443)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.135] An act to provide for the settlement of claims against the C.S.A., for property lost, captured, or destroyed while in the military service of the C.S.A., or which has been taken or impressed for their use, 1864; 228387 (Box 4, Folder C444)
  - Mr. Simpson's amendment to impressment bill, to provide for furnishing domestic supplies to the government, 1864; 228386 (Box 4, Folder C450)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.176] An act to authorize the consolidation of companies, battalions, and regiments, 1864; 228385 (Box 4, Folder C451)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.203] An act to protect the C.S.A. against frauds and to provide remedies against officers and employees of the government committing them, 1864; 228384 (Box 4, Folder C454)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.214] An act to define and punish conspiracy against the C.S.A., 1864; 228383 (Box 4, Folder C455)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.230] An act to amend an act to provide revenue from commodities imported from foreign countries, May 21, 1864; 228382 (Box 4, Folder C458)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.231] An act to exempt from taxation loans made on hypothecation of non-taxable bonds, 1864; 228381 (Box 4, Folder C459)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.232] An act to exempt from taxation the capital of bonds and certificates issued by the C.S.A., 1864; 228380 (Box 4, Folder C460)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.233] An act to consolidate and amend the laws relative to impressments, 1864; 228379 (Box 4, Folder C461)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no. 239] An act to organize the Supreme Court, 1864; 228378 (Box 4, Folder C462)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.240-Secret] A bill to provide for the establishment of a Bureau of Special and Secret Service, 1864; 228377 (Box 4, Folder C463)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.267-Secret] A bill to suspend the privilege of writ of Habeas Corpus... for a limited time, 1864; 228376 (Box 4, Folder C467)
  - C.S.A. Amendment to the bill to provide more effectually for the reduction and redemption of currency, 1864; 228375 (Box 4, Folder C469)
  - C.S.A. [House Bill no.274] A bill to increase the pay of marines to that received by the infantry of the army, 1864; 228374 (Box 4, Folder C471)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.275] A bill to authorize the employment of instructors for the acting midshipman of the navy, and to regulate their rank and pay, 1864; 228373 (Box 4, Folder C472)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.276] A bill making an appropriation to erect additional quarters for acting midshipmen at Dreury's Bluff, 1864; 228372 (Box 4, Folder C473)
  - C.S.A. [House of Representatives, no.277] A bill making an appropriation for the removal of the naval ropewalk and erection of the same, 1864; 228371 (Box 4, Folder C474)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.278] A bill to increase the number of acting midshipmen in the navy, and to prescribe the manner of appointment, 1864; 228370 (Box 4, Folder C475)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.279] A bill to provide for the transfer of certain mechanics, artizans, and other persons, from the army to the navy, 1864; 228369 (Box 4, Folder C476)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.280] An act to impose a duty on tobacco and an additional duty on cotton exported from the C.S.A., 1864; 228368 (Box 4, Folder C477)
  - C.S.A. Amendment to the bill to provide more effectually for the reduction and redemption of the currency, 1864; 228367 (Box 4, Folder C478)
  - C.S.A. Substitute for the bill [H.R.229] to provide more effectually for the reduction and redemption of the currency, 1864; 228366 (Box 4, Folder C479)
  - C.S.A. A resolution tendering negotiations for peace and a mitigation of the horrors of the war, 1864; 228365 (Box 4, Folder C480)
  - C.S.A. A resolution upon the subject of peace, 1864; 228364 (Box 4, Folder C481)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions relating to the war and negotiations for peace, 1864; 228363 (Box 4, Folder C482)
  - C.S.A. Amendment to bill to authorize the consolidation of companies, battalions and regiments, 1864; 228362 (Box 4, Folder C483)
  - C.S.A. Amendment to the bill to be entitled "An Act to authorize the consolidation of companies, battalions and regiments", 1864; 228361 (Box 4, Folder C484)
  - C.S.A. A resolution [relating to overtures of peace], 1864; 228360 (Box 4, Folder C485)
  - C.S.A. An act more effectually to provide for the reduction and redemption of the currency, 1864; 228359 (Box 4, Folder C486)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.285] An act to lay a tax for revenue to provide for the common defence and carrying on the government of the C.S.A., 1864; 228358 (Box 4, Folder C487)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.286] An act to levy and collect taxes for the common defence and for the support of the government for the year 1865, and to repeal certain tax laws, 1864; 228357 (Box 4, Folder C488)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.287] An act to authorize the 2nd Auditor of the Treasury, or a Commissioner, to be appointed by the Secretary of the Treasury with the consent of the President, to take proof as to the Expenditures of the State of Tennessee, in constructing military defences and the support of her army previous to its transfer to the Confederate government, 1864; 228356 (Box 4, Folder C489)
  - C.S.A. An act to provide for organizing, arming, and disciplining the militia of the C.S.A. and for governing such part of them as may be employed in the service of the C.S.A. and for calling them forth to execute the laws of the C.S.A., suppress insurrections and repel invasions, 1864; 228355 (Box 4, Folder C490)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.303] An act for the further organization of the field artillery of the C.S.A., 1864; 228354 (Box 4, Folder C493)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.307] An act authorizing the Secretary of the Treasury to borrow specie, to be applied to the redemption and reduction of the currency, 1864; 228353 (Box 4, Folder C494)
  - C.S.A. Amendments to the bill to be entitled "An act to authorize the consolidation of companies, battalions and regiments", 1864; 228352 (Box 4, Folder C495)
  - [House bil no.311] A bill to provide additional clothing and privileges to troops in the field, 1864; 228351 (Box 4, Folder C496)
  - C.S.A. Substitute for the bill [H.R.203]to protect the C.S.A. against frauds, 1864; 228350 (Box 4, Folder C497)
  - C.S.A. A bill to be offered as a substitute for the bill reported by the Committee on Military Affairs to consolidate companies, battalions, regiments and brigades, 1865; 228349 (Box 4, Folder C498)
  - C.S.A. Amendment to Section 3rd of the bill to be entitled "An act to authorize the consolidation of companies, battalions and regiments", 1865; 228348 (Box 4, Folder C499)
  - C.S.A. A bill to increase the efficiency of the cavalry of the C.S.A., 1865; 228347 (Box 4, Folder C500)
  - [House bill no.319] A bill more effectually to prevent and punish absenteeism and desertion in the army, 1865; 228346 (Box 4, Folder C501)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.320] A bill to change the mode of filling vacancies among commissioned officers of companies, battalions and regiments, 1865; 228345 (Box 4, Folder C502)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.288] An act authorizing the promotion of officers, non-commissioned officers and privates, for distinguished valor and skill or for peculiar competency and general merit, 1865; 228344 (Box 4, Folder C505)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.322] An act repealing certain abatements from the property tax and income tax, and amending the said tax laws, 1865; 228343 (Box 4, Folder C506)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.323] An act to provide payment for horses killed or lost in the service of the C.S.A., XXX; 228342 (Box 4, Folder C507)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.304] A bill to increase the efficiency of the cavalry of the C.S.A., 1865; 228341 (Box 4, Folder C508)
  - C.S.A. An act to provide for the more efficient execution of conscription, and for the arrest of deserters and absentees from the armies, 1865; 228340 (Box 4, Folder C509)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.326] An act to regulate the business of conscription, 1865; 228339 (Box 4, Folder C511)
  - C.S.A. Joint resolution of confidence in and thanks to President Jefferson Davis [by the Senate and House of the State of Florida], 1865; 228338 (Box 4, Folder C512)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions [in relation to peace and independence], XXX; 228337 (Box 4, Folder C513)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.183] An act to consolidate the public debt, 1865; 228336 (Box 4, Folder C515)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.184] An act to provide means to carry on the war, 1865; 228335 (Box 4, Folder C516)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.337-Secret] An act to levy additional taxes for the year 1865, for the support of the government, 228334 (Box 4, Folder C517)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions of the State of Texas, 1865; 228333 (Box 4, Folder C518)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.338] ... to levy and collect taxes for the year 1865 (2 copies), 228332 (Box 4, Folder C519)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.342] An act providing for the auditing and payment of properly authenticated claims, 1865; 228331 (Box 4, Folder C520)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.344] An act to provide for auditing and paying for horses and equipments taken from dismounted cavalrymen for the use of the government, 1865; 228330 (Box 4, Folder C522)
  - [House bill no.349] A bill to amend an act to organize forces to serve during the war, 1865; 228329 (Box 4, Folder C523)
  - C.S.A. (Secret) Resolution concerning additional taxes for the year 1865, XXX; 228328 (Box 4, Folder C524)
  - C.S.A. Amendments proposed by Mr. Baldwin to the impressment..., 1865; 228327 (Box 4, Folder C526)
  - [House bill no.361] A bill to provide for the establishment of a Bureau for Special and Secret Service, 1865; 228326 (Box 4, Folder C527)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.362-Secret] An act to provide means to carry on the war, 1865; 228325 (Box 4, Folder C528)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions adapted by the officers and men of the 57th Virginia Regiment, 1865; 228324 (Box 4, Folder C529)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions passed at a meeting of the Ninth Virginia Infantry, 1865; 228323 (Box 4, Folder C530)
  - C.S.A. Resolution concerning taxes, February 2, 1865; 228322 (Box 4, Folder C532)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions adopted by Bratton's Brigade, South Carolina Volunteers, January 30, 1865; 228321 (Box 4, Folder C535)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions adopted by Company "H", "I" and "K" Thirteenth Virginia Infantry, January 28, 1865; 228320 (Box 4, Folder C536)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions adopted by Humphrey's Mississippi Brigade, Army of Northern Virginia, February 3, 1865; 228319 (Box 4, Folder C537)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions adopted by McGowan's Brigade, South Carolina Volunteers, 1865; 228318 (Box 4, Folder C538)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.367] An act to increase the military force of the C.S.A., 1865; 228317 (Box 4, Folder C540)
  - C.S.A. Amendment to the Negro Soldier Bill, 1865; 228316 (Box 4, Folder C541)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.370-Secret] An act to organize forces to serve during the war, 1865; 228315 (Box 4, Folder C542)
  - C.S.A. A bill making appropriations to supply a deficiency in the appropriation for the Department of Justice fr the half year ending December 31, 1864, 1865; 228314 (Box 4, Folder C543)
  - C.S.A. Resolutions adopted by a meeting of the people of Powhatan, held in the courthouse on February court day, 1865, 228313 (Box 4, Folder C544)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.378] A bill to provide for the immediate payment of arrears dur to the army and navy, 1865; 228312 (Box 4, Folder C545)
  - C.S.A. Joint resolutions expressing the sense of Congress on the subject of the late peace commission, 1865; 228311 (Box 1865, Folder C547)
  - C.S.A. A bill to increase the efficiency of the cavalry of the C.S.A., 1865; 228310 (Box 4, Folder C548)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.386] A bill making further regulations for the taxation of banks and bank notes, and for the confiscation of such notes held by alien enemies, 1865; 228309 (Box 4, Folder C550)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.391] A bill to provide means to pay the army and navy, and carry on the war, 1865; 228308 (Box 4, Folder C551)
  - C.S.A. [House bill no.341]... requiring suit... against persons connected with the cotton bureau and cotton office in Texas, 1865; 228307 (Box 4, Folder C553)
  - C.S.A. Resolution in favor of private, non-commissioned officers of the line, 1865; 228306 (Box 4, Folder C555)
  - C.S.A. Amendment proposed to the bill [H.R.379], 1865; 228305 (Box 4, Folder C557)
  - C.S.A. Calendar, January 9, 1865; 228304 (Box 4, Folder C562)
  - C.S.A. Directory of the House of Representatives, 1864?; 228303 (Box 4, Folder C564)
  - C.S.A. Rules for the House of Representatives of the C.S.A. 18p., 1862; 228302 (Box 4, Folder C569)
  - C.S.A. House Committee on Claims Report... Mary Clark, 1863; 228301 (Box 4, Folder C570)
  - C.S.A. House Committee on Deceased Soldiers' Claims report, 1864; 228300 (Box 4, Folder C574)
  - C.S.A. House Committee on Foreign Affairs. Majority report, 1862; 228299 (Box 4, Folder C577)
  - C.S.A. House Committee on Foreign Affairs. Minority report... presented by Mr. Smith of Alabama, 1862; 228298 (Box 4, Folder C578)
  - C.S.A. House Committee on Quartermaster and Commissary Departments. Report of Committee... on case of Major Frank G. Ruffin, 1863; 228297 (Box 4, Folder C583)
  - C.S.A. House Committee on Rules report, 1865; 228296 (Box 4, Folder C586)
  - C.S.A. House Committee of Ways and Means. Minority report on the tax bill 4p. (photocopy), May 23, 1864; 228295 (Box 4, Folder C591)
  - XXX, 1863; 228294 (Box 4, Folder C.S.A. Evidence before House Committee, treatment of prisoners at Castle Thunder 58p.)
  - C.S.A. House report of Hospital Committee, 1862; 228293 (Box 4, Folder C593)
  - C.S.A. House Select Committee on Increase of Military Force... Mr. Rogers' minority report, 1865; 228292 (Box 4, Folder C597)
  - C.S.A. House Special Committee on the Charge of Corruption made in the Richmond Examiner, Jan. 7 1864 report, 228291 (Box 4, Folder C598)
  - C.S.A. House Special Committee on the Currency. Minority Report, December 30, 1863; 228290 (Box 4, Folder C599)
  - C.S.A. House Special Committee on the Pay and Clothing of the Army report, 1865; 228289 (Box 4, Folder C600)
  - C.S.A. House Special Committee on the Payment of Claims report, 1864; 228288 (Box 4, Folder C601)
  - C.S.A. House Special Committee on the Recent Military Disasters. Report, 1862; 228287 (Box 4, Folder C602)
  - C.S.A. President Davis Inaugural Address 8p. (Orig. and photocopy), February 18, 1861; 228286 (Box 4, Folder C607)
  - C.S.A. President Special... to the Congress, with accompanying documents, 1861; 228285 (Box 4, Folder C609)
  - C.S.A. President's message, November 18, 1861; 228284 (Box 4, Folder C612)
  - C.S.A. Message to the President of the Congress, transmitting communications from all the departments, except the War Department, 1862; 228283 (Box 4, Folder C617)
  - C.S.A. Message of the President., 1862; 228282 (Box 4, Folder C618)
  - C.S.A. President Message, January 12, 1863; 228281 (Box 4, Folder C622)
  - C.S.A. Message of the President transmitting a copy of an act of the Legislature of South Carolina, offering a guaranty [sic] by that state of the bonds of the C.S.A., 1863; 228280 (Box 4, Folder C624)
  - C.S.A. President Message, April 16, 1863; 228279 (Box 4, Folder C626)
  - President's Message, December 7, 1863; 228278 (Box 4, Folder C627)
  - C.S.A. Veto Message to the House, February 11, 1864; 228277 (Box 4, Folder C628)
  - C.S.A. President's Message, May 2, 1864; 228276 (Box 4, Folder C629)
  - C.S.A. President's Message, May 28. 1864; 228275 (Box 4, Folder C631)
  - C.S.A. President's Message, May 30, 1864; 228274 (Box 4, Folder C632)
  - C.S.A. President's Message, November 7, 1864; 228273 (Box 4, Folder C633)
  - C.S.A. Message of the President transmitting a communication from Hon. Howell Coff, former President of the Provisional Congress, relative to the preparation of copies of the journals of that body, and proceedings of the Convention, 1865; 228272 (Box 4, Folder C635)
  - C.S.A. Message of the President [submitting the report of the commissioners to confer with the President of the United States with a view to the restoration of peace, 1865; 228271 (Box 4, Folder C637)
  - C.S.A. Army General Orders no.1, March 20, 1862; 228270 (Box 4, Folder C643)
  - C.S.A. Army of Northern Virginia General Orders no.32, April 19, 1864; 228269 (Box 4, Folder C660)